Guide to the Peter E. Soderbergh Collection of Jehovah's Witnesses Materials, 1914-1995 AIS.1972.08
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Critical and Controversial Works, 1914-1995; IV.
  - How To Deal With Jehovah's Witnesses, 1967 (Box 11, Item 239)
  - What The Sects Teach: Jehovah's Witnesses, Seventh Day Adventists, Christian Science, Spritism, 1963 (Box 11, Item 240)
  - Jehovah's Witnesses and What They Believe (Box 11, Item 241)
  - Theocratic Aid to Kingdom Publishers, 1945 (Box 11, Item 242)
  - Theocratic Ministry School Guidebook, 1971 (Box 11, Item 243)
  - God's Kingdom of a Thousand Years Has Approached, 1973 (Box 11, Item 244)
  - True Peace and Security - From What Source?, 1973 (Box 11, Item 245)
  - God's "Eternal Purpose" Now Triumphing For Man's Good, 1974 (Box 12, Item 246)
  - Is This Life All There Is?, 1974 (Box 12, Item 247)
  - Scenario of the Photo-Drama of Creation, 1914 (Box 12, Item 248)
  - Man's Salvation Out of World Distress At Hand!, 1975 (Box 12, Item 249)
  - Good News To Make You Happy, 1976 (Box 12, Item 250)
  - Holy Spirit - The Force Behind the Coming New Order, 1976 (Box 12, Item 251)
  - Jehovah's Witnesses and the Question of Blood, 1977 (Box 12, Item 252)
  - Life Does Have a Purpose, 1977 (Box 12, Item 253)
  - Our Incoming World Government - God's Kingdom, 1977 (Box 12, Item 254)
  - "Singing and Accompanying Yourselves with Music in Your Hearts", 1966 (Box 12, Item 255)
  - Theocratic Ministry School Guidebook, 1971 (Box 12, Item 256)
  - Your Youth Getting the Best out of It, 1976 (Box 12, Item 257)
  - Commentary on the Letter of James, 1979 (Box 12, Item 258)
  - Choosing the Best Way of Life, 1979 (Box 12, Item 259)
  - Jehovah's Witnesses' Errors Exposed, 1959 (Box 12, Item 260)
  - Making Your Family Life Happy, 1978 (Box 12, Item 261)
  - "Let your Kingdom come", 1981 (Box 12, Item 262)
  - My Book of Bible Stories, 1978 (Box 12, Item 263)
  - Enjoy Life on Earth Forever!, 1982 (Box 12, Item 264)
  - You Can Live Forever in Paradise on Earth, 1982 (Box 12, Item 265)
  - Millions Now Living Will Never Die!, 1920 (Box 12, Item 266)
  - Jehovah's Witnesses, 1983 (Box 12, Item 267)
  - Survival Into a New Earth, 1984 (Box 12, Item 268)
  - United in Worship of the Only True God, 1983 (Box 12, Item 269)
  - Worldwide Security Under the "Prince of Peace", 1986 (Box 12, Item 270)
  - True Peace and Security: How Can You Find It?, 1986 (Box 12, Item 271)
  - Sing Praises to Jehovah, 1984 (Box 12, Item 272)
  - Reasoning from the Scriptures, 1985 (Box 12, Item 273)
  - Life - How did it get here? By evolution or by creation?, 1985 (Box 12, Item 274)
  - "Look! I am Making All Things New" (Box 12, Item 275)
  - Jehovah's Witnesses Unitedly Doing God's Will Worldwide, 1986 (Box 12, Item 276)
  - The Government That Will Bring Paradise, 1985 (Box 12, Item 277)
  - Examining the Scriptures Daily 1986, 1985 (Box 12, Item 278)
  - Mankind's Search For God, 1990 (Box 12, Item 279)
  - Questions Young People Ask: Answers that Work, 1989 (Box 12, Item 280)
  - The Bible: God's Word of Man's?, 1989 (Box 12, Item 281)
  - The Greatest Man Who Ever Lived, 1991 (Box 12, Item 282)
  - Watch Tower Publications Index 1930-1985, 1986 (Box 12, Item 283)
  - Insight on the Scriptures, Vol 1. Aaron Jehoshua, 1988 (Box 12, Item 284)
  - Insight on the Scriptures, Vol. 2, Jehovah Zuzim, 1988 (Box 12, Item 285)
  - Revelation: It's Grand Climax At Hand!, 1988 (Box 12, Item 286)
  - Knowledge That Leads to Everlasting Life, 1995 (Box 12, Item 287)
  - New World Translation of the Holy Scriptures, 1984 (Box 12, Item 288)